

Rafay Khan

Web Developer

Hello I'm Rafay Khan, I specialize in React Native, CSS, Bootstrap, HTML, and JavaScript. While I have not yet had the opportunity to put these skills into practice professionally, I am confident in my ability to create professional websites and believe that I have the necessary skills and knowledge to be successful in this field.

Contact Info

+923-034-160-752

■ abdulrafaykhan857@gmail.com

Rafaykhan177.github.io/Rafay

Education

Unique High School

2005 - 2022

Skills

Front End Development

Expert

Adobe Photoshop

Expert

Adobe Premier Pro

Expert

Language

HTML CSS JAVA-SCRIPT REACT.JS

Work Experience

Content Creation

2019 - 2022

Conducting keyword research and optimizing content for search engines. Developing content strategies to align with clients' business goals and target audience.

Web Development

2019 - 2022

Creating responsive websites that look and function well on a variety of devices including desktop computers, tablets, and smartphones.

Website Designer

2019 - 2022

Developing user flows and journey maps to illustrate how users will navigate through the website or application.

For More Information

This Barcode Redirecto to My Personal Website Rafaykhan177.github.io/Rafay